[Music]
Hey this
[Music] Shop is
fine, wake up quickly [Music]
[Music]
Grandma, reach the market quickly [Music] Shop,
everyone has work
[Music]
Wherever you are today, find me,
which vehicles are closed, which vehicles are
hanging,
which
vehicles without helmet, you should
capture your photo quickly,
Grandma, then call the
police
[Music]
Uncle, hey
Baba, hey who are thousands
[Laughter]
[Music]
Hey
boy, there is
no camera
Babu, only one useless camera, empty helmet
photo, get up, the way is bad,
Baba, the way is
fine, the vehicle is fine, give the medical stop to the empty vehicle, give
everyone the way, hey, move the wheel, uncle,
oh uncle, get up, the
road is
not jammed, get up, if not, then there is no fine, fix the
road, get
up,
who is all this, quickly remove the old man, the
social media is getting spoiled, give the money and the road is
damaged [Laughter] get the road fixed, okay sir,
uncle, get up, this is the intention, get the
road fixed,
hey,
forget the money